<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BlackJack</string>
    <string name="finish">ProgressBar is finished.</string>

    <string name="supportHelpCenterPA2">\"Split\" - this action is only available if the player\'s
        hand contains two cards of the same value.
        The player doubles their bet, splits their hand in two, and takes two additional cards.
        The two hands are then played independently.</string>
    <string name="supportHelpCenterPA3"> \"Hit\" - the player takes another card.
        This action can be repeated until the value of the hand exceeds 21 points.</string>
    <string name="supportHelpCenterPA4">\"Double\" - the player doubles their bet, takes another card, and stands.</string>
    <string name="supportHelpCenterPA5"> \"Stand\" - the player takes no more cards and keeps their current hand.</string>
    <string name="supportHelpCenterPA6"> If the value of the player\'s hand exceeds 21 points, they lose the round. </string>

    <string name="supportHCDealer1"> Once all players have stood, the dealer turns their face-down card over.</string>
    <string name="supportHCDealer2">If necessary, the dealer can take additional cards until they have 17 or more points.
        If the dealer\'s score exceeds 21, all players who have not gone bust automatically win regardless of their score. </string>

    <string name="supportHCInsurance">Special case: if the dealer has a face-up ace, the players have the option to place an additional
        \"insurance\" bet equal to half of their original bet. Once all players have made a decision, the dealer looks
        at their face-down card. If the dealer has blackjack, a payout of 2:1 is paid on all "insurance" bets.
        If the dealer does not have blackjack, all insurance bets go to the pot and the game continues as usual. </string>

    <string name="supportHCCountingPoints">The following card values are used when counting points: the cards from 2 to 10 are worth
        a number of points equal to the card\'s face value. The card J,Q and K are worth 10 points. Ace is worth 1 or 11 depending
    on which point value prevents the hand from exceeding 21.</string>
    
    <string name="supportCS2">To learn more about the rules and the game interface, please go to \"Support\" in the main menu,
        then to the \"Help center\" tab. Note\: this is just a basic Blackjack tutorial that teaches you how to play,
        not how to win.</string>

    <string name="supportCS3">History of game events can be found on the "Notifications" tab in the personal messages menu.
        All your achievements and actions are displayed in chronological order beginning with the most recent. </string>

    <string name="supportCS4">The Lobby is a place where you can watch currently active games, learn more about them and
        choose the table you\'d like to join. Advanced players spend a lot of time studying in the Lobby, checking the average
        bank and observing players' behavior to get an advantage in the game. Choosing a table in the Lobby is very important in
        getting the best-suited game for you and increase your profits.</string>

    <string name="supportCS5">You will see the amounts you can raise your bet as chips you can tap to add the corresponding value
        to your bet. However, you can also turn on "raise control" in the settings. This will allow you to hold the "bet" button
        and slide your finger up to raise the bet.</string>


    <string name="supportCS6">This may be caused by an unstable Internet connection. When playing, please make sure your connection
        is stable. </string>

    <string name="supportCS7">A star symbol next to a fellow player\'s nickname means that this user is on your friends list.</string>

    <string name="supportCS8">To save and share a special moment from the game, tap the bottom left \"dots\" button, then tap the
        camera icon and choose one of the following options\: save on your device, send via e-mail, or post on Facebook wall.
        If e-mail is not on the list, ensure that you have e-mail set up on your device.</string>


    <string name="supportCP1">Registration is not needed to start playing. You can play as guest, but in this case your account
        will be linked to a certain device. If you would like to continue playing and have all your achievements and score saved,
        you will have to use this device. You will not be able to restore your guest account, if your device gets lost or broken.</string>


    <string name="supportCP2">After getting registered you will be able to create your game profile. All your achievements, chips,
        coins and property will be stored in this profile.</string>
    <string name="supportCP3">Please use the registration form provided in the game menu. You will have to enter your e\-mail,
        password and nickname. If you wish, you can also upload your userpic. We suggest that you use a real email, in order we
        will be able to help you restore your password. If you have a social network profile, you can use it as a game profile.</string>

    <string name="supportCP4">Your ID is of 9 or 10 digit number, indicated in your profile in the application or on the website.
        Please remember to provide your ID when contacting technical support.</string>

    <string name="supportCP5"> Unfortunately, you cannot change your login. But you can register a new account and choose any
        other username.</string>

    <string name="supportCP6"> To restore your password please tap "Forgot your password?" link and enter your data in the form
        provided. We suggest that you use a real email. In case you have used non-existent email address or the address you have
        indicated is not available anymore, please use our contact form to receive any further instructions from our technical
        support</string>

    <string name="supportCP7">An account cannot be deleted. If you wish, you can create a new account. Please note that you can
        use up to 20 accounts on one device (including the guest account)</string>

    <string name="supportCP8">To enter game profile, please tap the block with your userpic, name and balance in the main menu. </string>

    <string name="supportCP9">To change your nickname tap on your nickname in the profile settings (or pencil pic next to it)
        and enter a new one, than tap \"Done\".</string>

    <string name="supportCP10">Tap on your current userpic in the game profile settings. Select \"New\" in the drop-down menu,
        then take a picture or choose a photo from your device gallery or another existing photo. If you logged in for the first
        time using your Facebook account, your Facebook avatar will be used.</string>

    <string name="supportCP11">Enter \"Profile\" in the main menu, then tap the line beyond your avatar and enter a new status.
        Leave this field empty, if you do not want anything to be displayed in the status field.</string>

    <string name="supportCP12">\"Location\" indicates the region you are currently in. To update your location please tap corresponding
        icon in the game profile. To determine your location on the website profile please tap \"Determine\" next to \"Location\"
        in your ID line on the right from the userpic</string>

    <string name="supportCP13">Please, make sure that the location settings on your device are activated and our application has
        access to it. If the location is not determined at specified settings, then try to reinstall the application and allow the
        determination of the location when you first start it. </string>

    <string name="supportCP14">You can buy property with chips or coins. Property does not change anything in the game process,
        but can indicate your game status. To buy property, please sign up to your account, tap \"Property\" and use purchase menu.
        You can give property to your friends or any user you like. To sell property please use a corresponding option in the game
        profile menu. Please take into account that you will get back only 10% of the price. When selling a property given to you
        by other players, you do not receive anything. Objects are just removed from your profile</string>

    <string name="supportCP15">Sitting at the table please tap on the glass icon next to your userpic, then choose a gift.
        Gift will be displayed next to the player\'s avatar. Property will be displayed in the corresponding tap of the user\'s
        profile. Please note, that the gifts are temporary, unlike property that is permanent. The gifts last as long as you play
        at one table, or several days, if they are VIP gifts</string>

    <string name="supportCP16">Tap glass or house icon next to player\'s userpic. Choose the gift and confirm the purchase.
        To give gifts to all the players at the table please choose \"buy for all\" in the purchase menu.</string>

    <string name="supportCP17">In case you do not like the gift you have bought or you have been given, you can substitute it
        with a new one. Tap on the current gift (the spot where you usually see the glass icon), then choose a new one. Then it
        will be displayed next to your avatar. In the exactly same way you can substitute other player's gift. Besides, gifts
        disappear when you exit the app. VIP gifts are the only exception. </string>

    <string name="supportCP18">According to Facebook rules, users cannot buy alcohol and tobacco while playing in this social
        network.</string>

    <string name="supportCP19">Achieves is an indicator of your gaming progress. To look through the list of achieves please go
        to the profile and tap \"Achiev\'s\". Tap the achieve to know what did you receive it for. You can also look through your
        achieves on the website profile.</string>

    <string name="supportCP20"> In the mobile apps some icons are hidden in the slighting panel - it is shown with page indicators
        in the lower right corner of the main menu. With the move of your finger you can go to Tournaments, Invite, Store, Tutorial
        and Signing out your profile. </string>


    <string name="supportGS1">To enter game settings you need to tap the gear icon in the upper right angle of the main menu.</string>

    <string name="supportGS2">Automatically game language is the same as configured in your device. However,
        you can select English, available in any version of the game. For this enable "Localization" option in the game settings. </string>


    <string name="ChangeAvatar"> To change your avatar, go to your profile and tap the avatar, then choose a default picture,
        take a photo, or upload a photo. Also, you are able to change your avatar on www.pokerist.com. Log into your account
        on the website, then aim a cursor on your nickname and select the \"Change avatar\" option. Certain types of avatars
        cannot be used in our game. Also, please remember that our games are 12\+. Please abstain from using images with any
        text symbols, images of cigarettes and alcohol, any messages or logos from other poker rooms, immodest clothing, pictures
        with weapons and any images that encourage hatred due to religion, nationality and so on.</string>


    <string name="Nickname">To change your nickname, log into your profile and tap your nickname, then enter your new one.
        You can also use emojis for your nickname. To change your status, log into your profile and tap on your status above
        your avatar or on the \"Say something to your friends\" line. Once here you can enter your new status. \nIf you still have any
        problem with your nickname/status please contact us. </string>

    <string name="RegisterAccount"> To play, it is enough to simply enter the application \- this creates a guest account.
        The guest account is linked to your device and can be lost if your device is lost or corrupted, if the OS is reinstalled
        on the device or if there is a system error on the device. We recommend that you register an account using your email
        address or Facebook account. By registering, you ensure that your game progress will be saved. Please note that only an
        account registered to an email address has a password. lithe email address you initially provide is unavailable to access,
        it will be very difficult to reset your password or gain access to your account if you forget your password. \nPlease follow
        the instruction below to register your Pokerist account. Once registered, you will be able to play on any device with this
        profile as all of your progress and friends will be saved to the account. \n1.Click \"Sign-in\". \n2.Click "New account".
        \n3.Follow the steps to complete registration.</string>


    <string name="lostAccount"> Don\'t worry, we\'ll be able to help you get your account access back! Please provide us with the
        following information about your lost account using the form below: \n1. What avatar did this account have? \n2. Nickname?
        \n3. The number of chips/gold that this account had? \n4. Was the account a guest account or was it registered?</string>


    <string name="findId">You can see your ID in your profile. It is the set of numbers (for example 49\-8957\-6014) under your
        username. To find out your ID number, enter your profile and you will see your ID to the right of your avatar. This number
        is unique for each player and it cannot be changed \- only you can see it in your profile. You can share this number with
        your friend, so they can find you in the game.</string>


    <string name="hackedAccount"> If you\'ve discovered that your account has been hacked, immediately log on to our website and
        change your password. If you use a simple password on your e-mail account, we strongly recommend that you change that one too.
        After changing your password, contact tech support. In some cases, you\'ll need to answer a few questions to confirm that
        the account belongs to you.</string>


    <string name="CantBuyChips">Sometimes your network or device settings may cause an error when you open the store. Please check
        whether the store and rules load. If they do not, please describe these symptoms to our support department to get a quick
        solution from us. A screenshot of the error will help us solve your problem faster. \nAndroid \- In-app Purchases Locked \nTo
        check whether your in\-app purchases are locked, go to Play Market -Press the menu icon - Settings - Parental Control.
        Ensure that parental control is switched off. </string>


    <string name="freeChips">Depending on the platform you play on, you have various options for getting free chips. You can find
        all our advertisement offers in the in-game store. You can watch video ads, complete quests and get a daily bonus. In
        addition, you can get rewards for completing quests and participate in promotional events on our Facebook group. Don\'t
        worry if you\'ve run out of chips, you always have the ability to get free chips or buy yourself a few to increase your
        balance. </string>

    <string name="earnAndUseChips">You can earn coins by joining our groups on social networks (Facebook,Twitter, Instagram) to
        take part in the competitions held there. You can win free chips as well as coins! You can also purchase gold coins in our
        store or get them by taking a prize-winning place in the weeklytournament. We\'re looking forward to seeing you on our
        social networkpages! \nYou can use coins to buy property either for yourself or as a gift to other players. You can also
        use coins to speed up assembling card collections, buy and give gifts at a table or move on to the next round of
        a Shootout tournament on Pokerist, if you didn't win the previous round.</string>

    <string name="transferChips">How Do I Transfer Chips To Another Player? Giving a gift of chips is an excellent way to make new
        friends or help your current ones! You can transfer chips to friends and other players directly while you play. The maximum
        number of chips you can transfer to other players is 100,000. To transfer chips to friends, visit your friend\'s profile
        from the main game menu, tap the chip icon with a little arrow and select the amount of chips you want to send. To transfer
        chips to other players during play, tap the other player's avatar at the table, press the button of the chip with an arrow
        and select the amount of chips you want to send. </string>

    <string name="chipsGone">Please indicate the sum you hhave lost and the date when the loss occured. Indicate the reason for the
        loss(e.g. a disconnection) if you know it.</string>

    <string name="lostGame">Don\'t forget to check the rules of the game in our Help Center. If you still have a question please contact
        our support team and attach the following information to your request: the date and time of the game along with information
        about your or dealer's cards.</string>

    <string name="dealerCardCheck">Please note, the game rules may differ depending on the casino and there may also be a lot of
        differences and variations. In our app, the classic Blackjack rules are used, when the dealer offers you an insurance
        option only if they received an Ace as their first card. You can learn more about the current game rules in the \"Support\"
        section, \"Help center\" tab. </string>

    <string name="loose21">According to the rules of the game,blackjack is 21 points scored with two cards. If you score 21 with
        three or more cards,you will loose with dealer if they get 21 points with two cards exactly</string>

    <string name="splitCards">If the first two cards you are dealt have the same rank tou have the option to split them in two hands.
        In this case, you can play each hand in turn and have a chance to win with either hand</string>

    <string name="disconnectedTournament">We\'re very sorry to hear that your tournament was interrupted in such an unpleasant manner.
        We understand how frustrating this must have been. \nPlease contact us and provide them with information about the date, time
        and fee of the tournament during which the error occurred.</string>


<string name="locationNotSet"> Please enter your profile and update your location, then allow it to be used, then wait several seconds.
    Your location should change. If this does not occur, try reinstalling the application and repeat the same actions again. Please
    contact us if your location does not update after reinstalling. </string>

    <string name="hideLocation">Location in our game helps you find your friends to play with, but we respect your right to hide.
        Please contact us to help you with this request.</string>

    <string name="manyAccountsDevice"> According to the User Conditions of KamaGames\' products, you can have no more than 4
        accounts at once. If you have received this error message, try to log in from the account which you registered first on
        your device. If this does not help, you\'ll need to log in from another device. Contact our support service if you have
        difficulties completing these instructions. </string>

    <string name="freeChipsSection"> If you didn\'t receive rewards for video offers or quests sections, please contact our support
        team and be ready to answer some questions, our team will do their best to help you. \nPlease remember, that we have a limit
        of 20 videos in 24 hours. When you have watched them, the free chips tab will disappear. If you don't see offers at all,
        don\'t worry, our partners will add new offers shortly for you to enjoy. Make sure you visit this section again to get them. </string>

    <string name="crashesApp">The game may crash or freeze for various reasons. Before contacting support, please check your internet
        connection. If your internet connection is stable and fast, try restarting your device. If restarting does not help, try
        reinstalling the application from the official store for your device (App Store, Play Market etc.). If these tips do not
        help you, contact our support service. </string>


    <string name="problemWithInternet">Our game is a real-time online game and requires a stable Internet connection. If yourgame
        freezes or periodically crashes during gameplay, check the stability of your internet connection using a third-party service
        such as http://speedtestmett We strongly recommend a stable WiFi connection with broadband internet or a persistent mobile
        connection without artificial speed limits, such as 3G or LTE.</string>

    <string name="changeGame">In our game, you can access Texas Poker, Omaha, Slots, Set Poker, Split Bet Poker, Baccarat, Roulette
        and Blackjack from one application. To change the game press \"Select game\" button, which is located in the top central
        part of your starting screen, then choose the game you would like to play. We would like to remind you that you can use one
        account for all our games. Have fun playing! </string>

    <string name="dontLikeGift"> If you do not like a gift that you bought or received, you can exchange it fora more expensive gift.
        Tap the current gift (the \"gift\" icon is usually located in the same place), then buy the new gift. It will then be
        displayed next to your avatar. You can also exchange another player\'s gift. Gifts disappear after a certain time. It
        is worth remembering that VIP gifts for gold last longer than ordinary gifts. </string>

    <string name="disbaleGifts">You can disable the display of gifts at the game table if they distract you from playing.
    To do this, use the corresponding switch in the setting menu. Note that you will not be able to give or receive gifts if
        you do this</string>

    <string name="cantWriteMessageChat">While playing at a table, tap the chat icon in the lower right corner. If you don\'t
        see messages from the other players at the table, but see them in the chat window, go to \"Settings\"and turn \"Block Chat\"
        off If you still can\'t see messages from other players even in the chat window, please tap the \"LOCK\" icon in the lower
        right corner of the screen to check whether other players have been blocked from the chat. If the problem persists even
        after following these instructions please contact us.</string>

    <string name="deletePrivateMsg">Tap and hold your finger on the message you want to delete, then select the \"Delete\" option in
    the resulting menu. You can delete only your own message. This will also delete them for other participant in the conversation</string>

        <string name="blockChat">You can not only play at the game table, but also chat. Players\' messages are displayed in
            floating windows above their avatars. If a message from another player bothers you, you can block messages from
            them in a special menu by tapping the icon with a lock located next to the \"chat\" icon. Select the specific players
            whose messages you don\'t want to see. You can also block conversations from all players at once. To do this, enable
            chat blocking in the game settings. </string>
    
    <string name="dailyQuest">Please send us the full name of the quest and description of the problem. We\'ll try to solve
        it as quickly as possible   </string>


    <string name="problemWithAchievement">Please send us the full name of the achievement and description of the problem. We\'ll try to solve
        it as quickly as possible</string>

    <string name="dailyBonusQuestion"> If you want to get to know the details about the sum of daily bonus, or time when you\'ll
        be able to receive the next one, please click on the \"Daily bonus\" tab at the right bottom angle of the main screen.
        If you didn't receive your daily bonus, please contact us</string>

    <string name="propertyGift"> You can buy gifts and property for chips and gold coins. Property does not influence gameplay,
        but is an indicator of your success in the game. To buy property, enter your profile, tap the \"Property\" tab and use the
        purchase menu. You can give property to friends or players that you like. Property that you buy can be sold later by using
        the corresponding menu item in your profile. However, bear in mind that in this case you will only get 10% of the value back.
        Gifted property cannot be sold, only deleted. If you collect all the property in one category, you\'ll get some luxury
        property that cannot be purchased. \nGifts do not affect gameplay, but show your mood or attitude to another player.
        When sitting at a game table, press the "gift" button next to your avatar or the avatar of the player to whom you want
        to give a gift, then select . The gift will be displayed next to the player's avatar. Note that all the gifts, in contrast
        to property, disappear with time. They persist for the duration of the game at that table or for several days
        (for example, VIP gifts for gold).
</string>


    <string name="addFriendList">You can add a player to your friends list while sitting at the game table or you can find a friend
        using their nickname or ID. To add a friend through the search, enter the Friends menu in the upper left corner of the screen,
        then go to the "Search friends" tab and enter the nickname or ID of the player. To add a player at a table, tap on their avatar
        and tap the icon with the + symbol, then confirm the action.</string>

    <string name="joinFriendGame">While in the game\'s main menu, tap your friend\'s icon. If your friend is currently at a table,
        you\'ll see the \"table\" icon. Tap it, then press \"Play\". You can also invite a friend to play with you. Tap the \+ on a
        free position at your table and select a friend. Your friend will receive an invitation to play with you. </string>

    <string name="cantFindFriend">You can find a friend using their nickname or ID number. If you\'re experiencing a problems
    while seaching for a friend please contact support and indicate the id of the friend you want to add</string>

    <string name="deleteFriend">While in the game\'s main menu, press the Friends button in the upper left corner of the screen.
        Select the friend you want to delete and tap the icon with a \- symbol. After deleting the friend, you will not be able to
        join them at a table, invite them to play with you or send/receive private messages with them.</string>

</resources>
